Discover what lies behind closed doors.
The Housemaid is a mystery, thriller film directed by Paul Feig.
Trying to escape her past, Millie Calloway accepts a job as a live-in
housemaid for the wealthy Nina and Andrew Winchester.
But what begins as a dream job quickly unravels into something far more
dangerous—a sexy, seductive game of secrets, scandal, and power.
Millie Calloway, played by Sydney Sweeney.
Nina Winchester, played by Amanda Seyfried.
Andrew Winchester, played by Brandon Sklenar.
Enzo, played by Michele Morrone.
Cece Winchester, played by Indiana Elle.
Pam, played by Sarah Cooper.
The Housemaid is a 2025 American erotic psychological
thriller film directed by Paul Feig.
It is based on the 2022 novel by Freida McFadden, and stars
Sydney Sweeney, Amanda Seyfried, and Brandon Sklenar.
In the film, Millie Calloway, a young woman with a troubled past, becomes the live-in
housekeeper for a wealthy family whose household hides dark secrets.
The Housemaid premiered at the Axa Equitable Center in New York City on December 2,
2025, and was released in the United States by Lionsgate on December 19.
The film received positive reviews from critics and
grossed $294,8 million worldwide.
A sequel is in development, with Feig, Sweeney, and Morrone set to return.
The film explores themes of based on novel or book,
psychological thriller, housekeeper, attic, housemaid.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.